{
  "title": "Idioms with the phrasal verb break",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "After years of working for a shoddy employer I was finally able to ........ from that company and set up my own business  ",
      "answers": ["break off", "break away", "break out", "break up"],
      "correct": "break away"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Nasa is currently in the process of trying to work out how to avoid any more of its spaceships from......... on re- entry to Earth. ",
      "answers": [
        "breaking off",
        "breaking away",
        "breaking out",
        "breaking up"
      ],
      "correct": "break up"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Residents living in the immediate vicinity of the prison w who recently ........ out of goal. ",
      "answers": ["broke-off", "broke-away", "broke-out", "broke-up"],
      "correct": "broke-out"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "It can be very difficult for youg couples to......... a marriage when there are young children involved.",
      "answers": ["break off", "break away", "break out", "break up"],
      "correct": "break up"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I decided to ........ my realtionship with my girlfriendwhen I found out that she was seeing someone else.",
      "answers": ["break off", "break away", "break out", "break open"],
      "correct": "break off"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Be careful not to spill the yolk when you ........ the egg.",
      "answers": ["break out", "break off", "break open", "break down"],
      "correct": "break open"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "A burglar ........ when I was away on vacation and stole of my electronic goods.",
      "answers": ["broke into", "broke off", "broke open", "broke up"],
      "correct": "broke into"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Teachers in Sydney have decided to call a snap strike next week after negotiations with the State Government over a ten per cent pay increase ........ early this morning.",
      "answers": ["broke into", "broke down", "broke open", "broke up"],
      "correct": "broke down"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "A rebel Labor Party MP recently decided to ........ from his party and become and independent member electorate. ",
      "answers": ["break off", "break away", "break out", "break up"],
      "correct": "break away"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "I am always very worried that my car will ........ because it is already twenty years old.",
      "answers": ["break down", "break out", "break away", "break off"],
      "correct": "break down"
    }
  ]
}
